Darwin Fegarido



darwinfegarido@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/darwinfegarido



09565705207



https://dfegarido.github.io/portfolio/

Summary

I have worked as a full-stack developer since 2016, a period during which I have worked in different environments, from start-ups to international companies. I am a self-motivated and self-taught professional who likes to solve problems. I merge a passion for usability and user experience with technical knowledge to create cool digital experiences. My repertoire includes programming languages and tools such as ReactJS, Vue, NodeJS, Python, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Nginx, MongoDB, Redis, and Elasticsearch. I also deploy applications using cloud computing like AWS EC2, ECS, S3, Azure, Heroku, and Github, and configure CICD on Gitlab and Github.

Experience

Full Stack Javascript Developer

VISEO ASIA

Feb 2021 - Present (2 years 2 months)

- * Creates applications based on the user requirements and functionalities of client
- * Create website on Shopify
- * Creates web app using ReactJS and VueJS
- * Doing Backend using NodeJS Rest API
- * Deploying application to AWS ECS S3 EC2 and Heroku
- * Implementing CICD on Gitlab

Tools:

- * Typescript
- * Restfull API
- * NodeJS
- * ReactJS
- * VueJS
- * Heroku
- * Shopify
- * Postgresql
- * Mysql
- * MongoDB
- * Git



Frontend Web Developer

Quantum Crowd

Apr 2020 - Jan 2021 (10 months)

Maintain an Existing CMS and add features requested from clients

Tools:

- * Vue JS (PUG)
- * NodeJS

- * Jira
- * Swagger

Full Stack Developer

Taktyl Studios

Nov 2019 - Jul 2020 (9 months)

I build the Content Management system for Mobile

gaming, normalizing the data's and convert it to business analytics.

Tools:

- * JS(ES6)
- * NodeJS
- * ReactJS
- * React-Native
- * MongoDB
- * Mysql
- * Nginx
- * Angular
- * VueJS
- * Linux (CentOS)
- * Laravel

Projects: CMS, Mobile App Project.



Python Programmer

Feb 2016 - Nov 2019 (3 years 10 months)

- * Creates applications based on the user requirements and functionalities of client
- * Does website scraping
- * Generates Automation Project
- * Creates website using Django Web Framework

Tools that I've used: DJango, Flask, Restframework, BeautifulSoup, Selenium, AWS, Debian Distro, Pandas and Numpy



Mid Developer

New Oriental Club88 Corporation

Mar 2019 - Aug 2019 (6 months)

Its a POGO company, my main responsibilities here is to secure the data that we are fetching from our clients.

Tools:

- * Php
- * CentOS
- * MySQL
- * Nginx
- * CronJob



Full Stack / Python Developer

Skyluster Technology Inc.

May 2018 - Feb 2019 (10 months)

- *Creates ERC20 Token and Crowdsale using Solidity language and Deploy to Ethereum Network / Blockchain
- * Create a secured site (https) using React, Django web framework, via Nginx
- * Plans and creates a project as per client's request.
- * Creates APIs using GraphQL or Rest with Node Express

Tools:

- * Solidity
- * Ethereum Virtual Machine
- * Javascript (ES6)
- * Linux (Ubuntu)
- * Web3JS
- * ReactJS
- * Nginx



IT Specialist

Azal Arabia Furniture

Feb 2015 - Mar 2018 (3 years 2 months)

- * Supported the Sales Management Web Based System
- * Created simple company website
- * Maintained and supported all hardware and software resources to be efficient and free from viruses

Education



Honorio MC Lopez Institute

Certificate, Computer Hardware Technology/Technician 2010 - 2012

Skills

Python • REST API • Node.js • Amazon Web Services (AWS) • Linux • React.js • JavaScript • Vue.js • PostgreSQL • MySQL